Bethea-Welch VFW Post 7248 Ladies Auxilliary 137
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Bethea-Welch VFW Post 7248 Ladies Auxiliary Collection
1914-2004
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Veterans of Foreign Wars of the United States. Bethea Welch Post No. 7284. Ladies Auxiliary
137
23 cubic feet; 15 boxes
15 Boxes
The Bethea-Welch Ladies Auxiliary of the Post 7284 Veterans of Foreign Wars Post was an auxilliary of the first VFW post for eligible African American veterans in Washington, D.C. The collection documents the day-to-day business of the club and contains lists of officers, event and meeting programs, printed materials, officer lists, awards, as well as meeting minutes and notes. Of particular note are photographs and scrapbooks documenting VFW events.
Biographical / Historical
The Bethea-Welch Ladies Auxiliary was founded May 12, 1948, and catered to African American women who supported the predominately black Bethea-Welch VFW. In 1947, Rosaline Thompson met with Bethea-Welch Post Commander Albert T. Jones and the mothers, wives and daughters of veterans who served overseas to discuss creating a women's auxiliary. As with the veteran's post prior to its founding, there was not a VFW Ladies Auxiliary for black women in D.C. With 16 charter members, the Ladies Auxiliary began working with veterans, their families, area youth, local churches and orphanages. In the early 1950s, the women of Bethea-Welch were invited to join the Department of the District of Columbia Ladies Auxiliary and participate in national programs. Members collected toys for young children, visited local VA hospitals, fed homeless families during the holiday season, provided books for veterans and children, and implemented programs at area churches. Some of the most popular programs included the Book Shower for veterans, annual Sweet Day for children living in a local settlement house, Junior Girls for young women, and the Bethea-Welch marching band. Other organizations benefited from the work of Bethea-Welch including the Girl Scouts, Children's Hospital, Police Boys and girls Club, House of Ruth and Walker Whitman Clinic.
The Bethea-Welch Post 7284 Veterans of Foreign Wars Post was founded by David D. Dixon. At the time, there was not a VFW post for eligible African American veterans in Washington, D.C. After approaching the VFW of D.C., he was allowed to launch a new post for black veterans. The post's name was chosen in memory of Sargent Bethea, who was killed in World War I, and Captain George A. Welch, who died in action during World War II in Italy.
Scope and Contents
The Bethea-Welch VFW Post 7248 Ladies Auxilliary Collection documents the day-to-day business of the club and contains lists of officers, event and meeting programs, printed materials, officer lists, awards, as well as meeting minutes and notes. Of particular note are photographs and scrapbooks documenting VFW events.
Women; African Americans; Veterans; Social groups; Organizational Records; Scrapbooks; Photographs
- Series 1
  - By Laws and Booklet of Instructions, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Auxillary's Cancer Fund, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Award for Attaining 100 percent of 1985 membership by December 31 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Certificate of Appreciation to Leora Thompson for 1986-1988 Service (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Officers List Template, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Current Roster Corrections, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - New Addresses: Evelyn Jones and Olve Thomas, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blank Sheets with Letterhead, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Life Membership Application, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fortieth Anniversary Celebration, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Etiquette of the Stars and Stripes, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Joint Installation May 6th 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Communicator, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Patrons List, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ann Landers, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Application for life Membership, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Distribution of Reciepts - Disbursements and Cash Balance by Fund, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Active/Inactive Status Notes and Correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Observance of Veterans Day Notes, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Certificate of Appreciation Mrs. Leora Duggans Thomas, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Post and Auxillary Anniversary Well Wishers List, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Charter Members Initiated May 12 1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anniversary Celebration, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Revital Booklet, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pay Slip Booklet, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Property Stickers, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 40th Anniversary Celebration Howard Inn October 16 1988 Info (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sharter Members Initatives May 12 1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chartered Members as of October 24 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Headquarters Grand Army of the Republic - General Orders No. 11, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Building America Today for Tomorrow, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ladies Auxillary to VFW Pamphlet, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Buddy Poppy Day, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Early Historical Data, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Past VFW Ladies Department Presidents List, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1997 Hospital/VAVS Program Certificate (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Franklin P. Nash Methodist Church Certificate, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Membership Award for Attaining 100% of 1991 Membership by Dec 31 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Proceedings of the 43rd Annual National Encampment of the Ladies Auxillary, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - By Laws as Amended - 20th Surpreme Convention August 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Buddy Poppy Info, 1999-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - James P. Moran Reception Program, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Nation WWII Memorial Correspondence, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Bio, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Loyalty Day - 1995 Program DC Department VFW (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "An Anniversary Celebration" continued service to veterans, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "Dear Readers and Response" Washington Post Article, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Certificate of Recognition for Keeping the Promise to Our Hospitalized Veterans, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - That Freedom May Live Bethea Welch, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Podium Edition By Laws and Ritual, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Safety Tips Metrorail and Safe Kids Pamphlet, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bethea- Welch Ladies Auxillary Roster - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Ritual Booklet, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Observance of Veterans Day Memorial Service at Arlington, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Membership Award for 100 percent of 1977 membership by December 31 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Photograph: Auxillary Women, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Catherine Coleman President, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Rebecca Cannon, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mary Anderson - 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Lila Medley - 1976-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - ADA Winstead - 1960-1962 and 1984-1986, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth Tyler - 1968-1970, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - National Safety Award, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Membership Award for Attaining 100% of 1976 Membership by Dec 31 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Membership Award for 100 percent of 1998 Membership by December 31 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Community Service Award Second Place - 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Health and Happiness Certificate - 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Health and Happiness Certificate for Quota Fullfillment - 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Citation of Merit for Reporting over one hundred percent in membership, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Health and Happiness Certificate for Quota Fullfillment - 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Golden Anniversary Award - 1948-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ladies Auxillary VFW Magazine, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ladies Auxillary VFW Magazine, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ladies Auxillary VFW Magazine, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - VFW Auxillary Magazine, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fortieth Anniversary Celebration Program, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - VFW Recruitment Pamphlet, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Carbon Paper Notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Through the Eyes of a Child - 2004 Calender (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Jesus Photograph, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Health and Happiness Certificate for Quota Fullfillment - 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 25th Department Convention Pamphlet, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sunday October 24 1982 Programme (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - VFW Joint Installation Services April 17 1959 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 26th Department Convention June 26-27 1959 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Office Name and Auxillary Booklet, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 29th Department Convention Program, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 28th Department Convention June 1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1981-1982 Officer List Booklet With Addresses (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1960-1961 Officer List Booklet (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1961-1962 Officer List Booklet (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1960-1961 Officer List Booklet (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1980-1981 Officer List Booklet (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1979-1980 Officer Booklet (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1978-1979 Officer List Booklet (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1977-1978 Officer List Booklets (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1976-1977 Officer Booklet (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1982-1983 Officer List Booklet (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Silver Anniversary Banquet Inivitation, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Community of Hope Update, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Constitution of the United States, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ritual Booklet, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Official Program 81st National Convention, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - In Memoriam Past Department Presidents, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Auxillary Youth Christmas Party December 97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - The VFW Grace Stewart Memorial, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - In Memoriam Frances J. Dove, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - History and Officer List, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - VFW National Magazine, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - VFW National Magazine, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - VFW National Magazine, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - VFW National Magazine, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - VFW National Magazine, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - VFW National Magazine, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 61st Annual Veterans Day Ball, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Day Ball Pamphlet, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Safety Tips: Metro Buses Pamphlet, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mini vs. Flag, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Building Today for Tomorrow, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 54th Department Convention June 19-20 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Department Convention June 19-20 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 59th National Convention Official Program, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 59th National Convention New York, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 49th Department Convention June 1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Health and Happiness Certificate - 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Tyler Papers, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General Orders - 1980-81, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Membership Reunion Tea, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 54th Department Convention, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Auxillary Luncheon 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cards 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cards 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Notes/ Talking Points, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Trustees Audit, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - VFW Archives, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Misc, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Newletters, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - VFW Roster, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Officers - 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chairman 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Officer Lists, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Book 6 Officers, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Book 7 Officer List, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Security Attendance, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Certification of Support of the VFW National Home, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Attendance - 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Roster - 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Roster, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Roster, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Roster, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Roster, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Roster, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Washington Afro-American "VFW Aids Help Cookout" and Aid Cancer Fight Dinner, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Program Adel aide Gilliard Bourne, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hazel Mansell, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Americanism Award, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1962-1964 Evelyn Allen (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Lillian Miller, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1958-1960 Erma Frazier (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - VFW Bulletin August, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - VFW Bulletin, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Past Auxillary Presidents List, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - General Orders, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Internal Correspondence, 1957-1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Officer Lists 1, 1956-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Charter Member List, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - VFW Auxilliary Magazine, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - VFW Auxilliary Magazine, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - VFW Auxilliary Magazine, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - VFW Auxilliary Magazine - 1981, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bethea Welch Ladies Auxillary History, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bethea Welch Post History and Past President List, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Council Member no. 4 Elizabeth Tyler - 1984-1986 sign, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Eastern States Conference President Williams - 1995-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Photographs Speaker Cabinet Committee Ambassador, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Photographs Eric Holder and Members, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Obituary July 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Minutes 1/17/68 Note Card, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - VFW National Programs Report, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Power of Patriotism Pamphlet, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Voice of Democracy" 35th Annual Broadcast Scriptwriting Scholarship Program, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Day Arlington National Cemetery Nov 11 1981 Pamphlet (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - VFW - 1981 Congressional Banquet (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 62nd Annual Convention June 19-20 1981 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Committee for Memorial Pay Observances - 1981 Brochure (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to George Regarding Certificate of Attendance, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Memorial Day 1981 Tickets Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Upton Citizen Article July 10 1980 Millard and Dooley (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Army Times November 20 1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Holiday Volunteer Correspondence, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - National Salute to Hospitalized Veterans February 10 1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship AD/"Building America Together", 1982 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Veterans Day National Committee 28th Veterans Day National Ceremony Invitation, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Stan Mooney Ham, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - New Release and Public Announcement February 26 1982 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - 9th Annual National Salute to Hospitalized Veterans, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Management Opportunity Job Post, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - World Vision - Helping Children and Families-Check/ Donation Reciept, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Volunteer Services Correspondence, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Misc, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Minutes-Meeting April 5 1980 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Reorganization of Gainesville PAC/Beautification and Clean up, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Veterans Can Help POW/ MIA Suggestions, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Lite Bike/Bring Your Bike AD, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - V.F.W National Programs Report Forms, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - VAVS - Hospital Report, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Christmas Part National Children's Center for Retarded December Report, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - 33rd Anniversary Event Info, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Halloween Party Info, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Friends of Ruth Jone Message, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Washington Urban League Membership Renewal Correspondence, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence D.C General Hospital Contribution, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Community Activity Notes/Correspondence, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - V.F.W Newsletter Series, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Community Activity Chairman October Report, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Community Activity Chairman, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Contribution thank you for 95th birthday observance of statute of liberty, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - National Salute to Hospitalized Veterans, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Immaculate Conception Pupil Wins DC Contest, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Office Ballot Cards and White House Luncheon Tickets, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Washington Conference, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Thank you cards, undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Service of Rememberance for John R. McPherson, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - DC Voice of Democracy Winners Robin Dyson, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Wakeup America October 31 1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Children's Center Photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 35th Anniversary, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Visitation Dept. Commander Thomas Foley, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Days Services for 1981 at Arlington Cementary (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - D.C VFW and Auxillary- Phila. 1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - V.F.W 1975 Trip to Hawaii and 1986 Photographs 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bethea- Welch Post No. 7284 Position/name List, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mason's Parade Six Auxillary Members Particpated, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Check Photo Copies, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Annual Joint Installation Services Tuesday May 16 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Prevention of Blindness Contribution to United Givers Fund, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Thank you Cancer Aid and Research Fund Program, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - A Brief Note of Thanks - 1967 VGF Campaign, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Suit Party Christmas Holidays, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Have a Heart for Children Meriwether Home Children's Outing, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Underpriviledge Children going on Barge Trip, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - VAVS Advisory Committee Contribution Correspondence, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Annual Veterans Day Ball Committee, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - The D.C 5 W's, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Christmas Card, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Thank you for Clothing, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Thank you letter, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Thank you for American Flag, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Constitution Day - 180th Commemorization, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Rag Dolls and Toys for Junior Village Dolls and Toys and Administration Building, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Thank U Gram From Joseph S. Kosisky, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Sympathy Card, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Report of Buddy Poppers to be made at National Presidents Visitation, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - United Givers Fund Thank you Letters Correspondence, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - National Programs Correspondence, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Thank you for V.F.W Lancers Drum and Bugle Corps Funding, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - V.F.W National Programs Report Form and Questionaire, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Post Auxillary and Jr. Unit St. Valentines Dance at 5th Elizabeth Hospital, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Eastern States Conference By Laws, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Smart Bowling Apparel By Brunner, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Scrapbooks, 1955-1960 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1960-1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1968-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1977-1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Plaques, 1965-1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Plaques, 1965-1996 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Plaques, 1965-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Plaques, 1965-1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)